export const decks = [ champions = 
    //ODI WC
    {
        'question':'ODI WC 1975',
        'answer':'West Indies'
    },
    {
        'question':'ODI WC 1979',
        'answer':'West Indies'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 1983',
        'answer':'India'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 1987',
        'answer':'Australia'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 1992',
        'answer':'Pakistan'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 1996',
        'answer':'Srilanka'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 1999',
        'answer':'Australia'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 2003',
        'answer':'Australia'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 2007',
        'answer':'Australia'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 2011',
        'answer':'India'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 2015',
        'answer':'Australia'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'ODI WC 2019',
        'answer':'England'
    }
    //T20 WC 
    ,{
        'question':'T20 WC 2007',
        'answer':'India'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'T20 WC 2009',
        'answer':'Pakistan'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'T20 WC 2012',
        'answer':'West Indies'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'T20 WC 2014',
        'answer':'Srilanka'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'T20 WC 2016',
        'answer':'West Indies'
    }
    ,{
        'question':'T20 WC 2021',
        'answer':'Australia'
    }
]